(Sheldon:)I think we should
see other people.
What?!
(Sheldon:)Well, as a male, I have
an evolutionary drive
(Sheldon:)to perpetuate my DNA.
(Sheldon:)Restricting myself to a single
partner is against my nature.
We sleep together once a year!
(Amy:)You want other partners?
(Sheldon:)Don't blame me.
Blame your pal, biology.
(Sheldon:)He's the pervert pulling
the strings here.
(Amy:)You wanna see other people?
Go see other people.
(Penny:)I hope one of those people is a
monkey, 'cause this is bananas.
(Leonard:)You can make jokes,
but if this keeps up,
(Leonard:)he's gonna move
back in here.
(Penny:)All right. Well, let's just get them
apart for a while
(Penny:)so they can cool down.
(Leonard:)Good.
(Leonard:)Then before we
reintroduce them,
(Leonard:)we'll give him one
of her sweaters
(Leonard:)so he can get used
to her scent again.
(Penny:)So it's okay for you
to joke around?
(Leonard:)No, that's actually
what we did with him
(Leonard:)when Howard came
back from space.
(Howard:)Honey, how ya feeling?